Hello friends welcome back you are on my channel
ICICI Prudential Pension
Funds Management Company Limited
if we talk about qualification then
they have
not mentioned any qualification here but here also all the
companies which are hiring here are
asking for graduates okay some are
also taking intermediate so if you are an
intermediate even for interview then you
apply for it then their return comes okay
then there they will give the full form where
they will give all the details about what your
qualification should be okay about your
work so well here they have also
told a little in short
okay so first you apply here
then whatever qualification etc. will be there
okay and whatever details they send what actually will they
send in the details let me
tell you that to work in any insurance
company you have to
qualify the IRDAI exam okay so
wherever you apply for insurance
and if you have
not qualified the IRDAI exam then first of
all what company  They will
charge you the IRTAI fee, okay, this is your
center level exam, the fee is around Rs.
500, okay, so you have to pay the
fee, then they will provide you with one month's training,
okay, then after giving the training, you can
easily qualify that exam because the
questions that come are
related to that training, so if
you read the PDF etc. carefully and
also attend the lectures etc., if you do
not understand then you can easily
qualify it, so
after qualifying it, if you become an insurance agent of ICICI Prudential
Pension Fund Management Company,
you will get an ID card,
okay, after that they will again provide you training on their
products, and
after that you will become a freelance insurance agent
walker, all the details are not written here,
but I know because I have
made many videos on this, especially on urgent matters,
okay, so here you simply have to
apply first, after that when Revolt
comes, they will provide you with all the details,
okay, so if  If you like my channel then
subscribe to it because I keep
providing such latest job updates.